# Wei Shao

17415 CH St-Marie KIRKLAND QC H9J 2L3 514-659-5789 stone shao@hotmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Seeking a Software Developer position to develop mobile applications using the most modern of development tools and the latest cutting edge methodologies learned at John Abbott College. With my many years of study, I am now ready to enter the IT field to contribute in a most meaningful way.

### **RELEVANT SKILLS**

- Mobile programming: Android, Web APIs
- Java, Enterprise Java Beans, and SQLite

#### **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

- Web programming: HTML5, CCS3, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP5
- MySQL, micro-framework PHP Slim, Twig, AJAX
- Dream Weaver CS6, Git / SourceTree, XAMPP
- .Net: C#, Visual Basic, ASP.NET, Access, MS SQL Server
- Design data structures and algorithms

## **EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS**

John Abbott College (Montreal)

Sep 2016 to Oct 2017

**AEC: Internet Programming and Development** 

**Concordia University (Montreal)** 

Jan 2003 to Aug 2006

**Bachelor Degree** 

Major: Computer Engineer

## **CAREER SUMMARY**

9179-0519 Quebec Inc. (Retail)

Feb 2007 to Feb 2017

**Position: Manager** 

FAW Group R&D Center, Changchun, China

Sep 1995 to Sep 2002

Position: AutoCAD Designer